Guide to the Ernest J. Sternglass papers, [ca. 1952-2008]
Sternglass, Ernest J. papers
- Alphabetical File List
  - Notebook 88, April 5, 1978 - April 19, 1978 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 89, April 19, 1978 - April 27, 1978 (Box 89)
  - Notebook 90, May 8, 1978 - June 7, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 91, June 7, 1978 - June 29, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 92, June 29, 1978 - July 24, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 93, July 24, 1978 - September 7, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 94, September 7, 1978 - October 18, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 95, October 18, 1978 - December 3, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 96, December 3, 1978 - December 22, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 97, December 22, 1978 - January 6, 1979 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 98, January 6, 1979 - January 14, 1979 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 99, January 14, 1979 - January 30, 1979 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 100, January 30, 1979 - June 10, 1979 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 101A, June 10, 1979 - October 29, 1979 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 101B, June 10, 1979 - September 7, 1979 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 102, September 7, 1979 - October 9, 1979 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 103, October 10, 1979 - November 6, 1979 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 104, November 7, 1979 - January 24, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 105, January 24, 1980 - February 26, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 106, February 26, 1980 - April 23, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 107, April 23, 1980 - July 13, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 108, July 13, 1980 - July 26, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 109, July 26, 1980 - September 2, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 110, September 2, 1980 - September 10, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 111, September 10, 1980 - October 6, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 112, October 6, 1980 - October 21, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 113, October 21, 1980 - October 29, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 114, October 24, 1980 - November 17, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 115, November 17, 1980 - December 6, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 116, December 6, 1980 - January 13, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 117, January 13, 1981 - February 13, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 118, February 13, 1981 - March 23, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 119, March 23, 1981 - April 5, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 120, April 5, 1981 - May 14, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 121, May 14, 1981 - June 9, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 122, June 9, 1981 - June 21, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 123, June 27, 1981 - July 3, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 124, July 6, 1981 - July 29, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 125, July 29, 1981 - September 5, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 126, September 5, 1981 - September 25, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 127, September 25, 1981 - October 17, 1981 (Box 90)
  - Notebook 128, October 17, 1981 - November 16, 1981 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 129, November 16, 1981 - December 19, 1981 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 130, December 19, 1981 - December 30, 1981 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 131, December 30, 1981 - January 10, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 132, January 10, 1982 - January 25, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 133, January 25, 1982 - February 19, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 134, February 19, 1982 - March 14, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 135, March 14, 1982 - June 4, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 136, June 4, 1982 - June 27, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 137, June 27, 1982 - July 13, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 138, July 13, 1982 - August 27, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 139, August 27, 1982 - September 13, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 140, September 13, 1982 - October 3, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 141, October 3, 1982 - October 30, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 142, October 30, 1982 - December 2, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 143, December 2, 1982 - February 9, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 144, February 9, 1983 - February 27, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 145, February 27, 1983 - March 22, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 146, March 22, 1983 - May 2, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 147, May 2, 1983 - May 31, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 148, June 1, 1983 - June 17, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 149, June 17, 1983 - July 11, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 150, July 13, 1983 - October 1, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 151, October 1, 1983 - November 26, 1983 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 152, November 26, 1983 - January 8, 1984 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 153, January 8, 1984 - February 18, 1984 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 154, February 18, 1984 - March 8, 1984 (Box 91)
  - Notebook 155, March 8, 1984 - April 17, 1984 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 156, April 17, 1984 - May 13, 1984 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 157, June 13, 1984 - August 21, 1984 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 158, August 21, 1984 - September 19, 1984 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 159, September 19, 1984 - October 22, 1984 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 160, October 22, 1984 - December 9, 1984 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 161, December 9, 1984 - February 1, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 162, February 1, 1985 - February 20, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 163, February 20, 1985 - April 20, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 164, April 20, 1985 - June 5, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 165, June 5, 1985 - July 16, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 166, July 16, 1985 - September 28, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 167, September 28, 1985 - October 18, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 168, October 18, 1985 - October 31, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 169, October 31, 1985 - November 10, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 170, November 10, 1985 - November 22, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 171, November 22, 1985 - December 5, 1985 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 172, December 5, 1985 - January 28, 1986 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 173, January 28, 1986 - March 6, 1986 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 174, March 6, 1986 - May 2, 1986 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 175, May 2, 1986 - September 7, 1986 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 176, September 7, 1986 - October 7, 1986 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 177, October 7, 1986 - November 13, 1986 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 178, November 13, 1986 - December 20, 1986 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 179, December 20, 1986 - January 27, 1987 (Box 92)
  - Notebook 180, January 27, 1987 - February 9, 1987 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 181, February 9, 1987 - March 12, 1987 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 182, March 12, 1987 - April 10, 1987 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 183, April 10, 1987 - May 22, 1987 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 184, May 22, 1987 - July 21, 1987 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 185, July 21, 1987 - September 21, 1987 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 186, September 21, 1987 - November 19, 1987 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 187, November 19, 1987 - December 24, 1987 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 188, December 24, 1987 - January 30, 1988 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 189, January 30, 1988 - March 24, 1988 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 190, March 24, 1988 - June 21, 1988 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 191, June 21, 1988 - August 23, 1988 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 192, August 23, 1988 - September 11, 1988 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 193, September 11, 1988 - September 28, 1988 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 194, September 28, 1988 - November 2, 1988 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 195, November 2, 1988 - December 7, 1988 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 196, December 7, 1988 - January 3, 1989 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 197, January 3, 1989 - February 13, 1989 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 198, February 13, 1989 - March 6, 1989 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 199, March 6, 1989 - April 16, 1989 (Box 93)
  - Notebook 200, April 16, 1989 - May 16, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 201, May 16, 1989 - June 8, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 202, June 8, 1989 - June 29, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 203, June 29, 1989 - August 7, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 204, August 7, 1989 - August 24, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 205, August 24, 1989 - September 29, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 206, September 29, 1989 - October 22, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 207, October 23, 1989 - November 16, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 208, November 16, 1989 - December 15, 1989 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 209, December 15, 1989 - January 25, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 210, January 25, 1990 - February 11, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 211, February 11, 1990 - March 28, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 212, March 28, 1990 - April 11, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 213, April 11, 1990 - April 24, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 214, April 24, 1990 - June 17, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 215, June 17, 1990 - August 3, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 216, August 3, 1990 - October 1, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 217, October 1, 1990 - November 25, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 218, November 25, 1990 - December 18, 1990 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 219, January 18, 1991 - February 15, 1991 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 220, February 18, 1991 - April 4, 1991 (Box 94)
  - Notebook 221, April 4, 1991 - June 12, 1991 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 222, June 12, 1991 - July 17, 1991 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 223, July 17, 1991 - October 9, 1991 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 224, October 9, 1991 - November 7, 1991 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 225, November 7, 1991 - December 17, 1991 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 226, December 17, 1991 - January 21, 1992 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 227, January 21, 1992 - March 17, 1992 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 228, March 17, 1992 - May 23, 1992 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 229, May 23, 1992 - July 2, 1992 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 230, July 2, 1992 - August 26, 1992 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 231, August 26, 1992 - October 10, 1992 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 232, October 10, 1992 - December 12, 1992 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 233, December 12, 1992 - January 25, 1993 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 234, January 25, 1993 - April 10, 1993 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 235, April 10, 1993 - June 3, 1993 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 236, June 3, 1993 - August 12, 1993 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 237, August 12, 1993 - September 16, 1993 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 238, September 16, 1993 - October 11, 1993 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 239, October 11, 1993 - December 15, 1993 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 240, December 15, 1993 - February 24, 1994 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 241, February 24, 1994 - May 18, 1994 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 242, May 18, 1994 - July 6, 1994 (Box 95)
  - Notebook 243, July 6, 1994 - September 9, 1994 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 244, September 9, 1994 - November 2, 1994 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 245, November 2, 1994 - December 4, 1994 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 246, December 4, 1994 - January 20, 1995 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 247, January 20, 1995 - February 22, 1995 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 248, February 22, 1995 - April 7, 1995 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 249, April 7, 1995 - June 11, 1995 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 250, June 11, 1995 - July 30, 1995 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 251, July 30, 1995 - September 7, 1995 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 252, September 7, 1995 - October 25, 1995 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 253, October 25, 1995 - December 14, 1995 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 254, December 14, 1995 - January 12, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 255, January 12, 1996 - February 19, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 256, February 19, 1996 - May 2, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 257, May 2, 1996 - June 2, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 258, June 2, 1996 - July 31, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 259, July 31, 1996 - September 11, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 260, September 11, 1996 - November 7, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Notebook [Low Level Radiation], September 17, 1996 - May 20, 1999 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 261, November 7, 1996 - November 29, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 262, November 29, 1996 - December 16, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 263, December 16, 1996 - January 4, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 264, January 4, 1997 - February 20, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 265, February 20, 1997 - May 2, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 266, May 2, 1997 - June 30, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 267, June 30, 1997 - November 23, 1997 (Box 96)
  - Notebook 268, November 23, 1997 - February 8, 1998 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 269, February 8, 1998 - April 4, 1998 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 270, April 4, 1998 - May 13, 1998 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 271, May 13, 1998 - June 23, 1998 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 272, June 28, 1998 - September 9, 1998 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 273, September 9, 1998 - November 18, 1998 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 275, December 30, 1998 - June 4, 1999 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 276, June 4, 1999 - July 1, 1999 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 277, July 1, 1999 - September 14, 1999 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 278, September 14, 1999 - November 24, 1999 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 279, November 24, 1999 - February 1, 2000 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 280, February 1, 2000 - July 29, 2000 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 281, July 31, 2000 - December 6, 2000 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 282, December 6, 2000 - March 7, 2001 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 283, March 7, 2001 - July 24, 2001 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 284, July 24, 2001 - January 3, 2002 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 285, January 3, 2002 - May 7, 2002 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 286, May 7, 2002 - August 15, 2002 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 287, August 15, 2002 - Jauary 2, 2003 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 288, January 2, 2003 - September 5, 2003 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 289, September 5, 2003 - June 1, 2004 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 290, June 2, 2004 - January 25, 2005 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 291, January 25, 2005 - March 27, 2005 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 292, March 27, 2005 - July 6, 2005 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 293, July 7, 2005 - October 27, 2005 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 294, October 27, 2005 - February 14, 2006 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 295, February 14, 2006 - July 13, 2006 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 296, July 13, 2006 - December 19, 2006 (Box 97)
  - Notebook 297, December 20, 2006 - June 4, 2007 (Box 97)
  - 9 boxes of unprocessed material (Box 98-106)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Resonant particles proceedings, second topical conference, Ohio University, Athens, Ohio, June 10-12, 1965 containing the Sternglass article "New Evidence for a Molecular Structure of Meson and Baryon Resonance State" has been removed. A copy is available in the Physical Sciences Library as call # QC721.C743 1965